wwol.info 2011-12-31

# WWOL.info

**WWOL Info PRIVACY POLICY**

The **WWOL.info** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.

**Third Party Advertising**

The **WWOL** use advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to our and other websites in order to provide advertisements on the **WWOL** and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to the **WWOL** , our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**Personal** **Information**

The **WWOL** do not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on the **WWOL.info** , we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

**External** **Links**

The **WWOL.info** contains links to other sites, and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**Contacting WWOL.info**

If you have any questions or concerns about the **WWOL** 's **Privacy Policy** or its implementation, you may contact us.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

The **WWOL.info** may update this **Privacy Policy** from time to time, and so you should review this **Policy** periodically. If there are significant changes to the **WWOL** information practices, you will be provided with appropriate online notice. You may be provided other privacy-related information in connection with your use of offerings from the **WWOL** , as well as for special features and services not described in this **Policy** that may be introduced in the future.
